Matías Gaete Ponce

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Details

Santiago

Chile

+569 66067120

mati.gaete.ponce@gmail.com

Skills

Teamwork skills Interpersonal Communication Skills Web development Frontend development

Fast learning

Empathetic

Languages

English – A2 Spanish – Native

Profile

Software Engineer with 3 years of experience in the area of software development, I am a proactive person in the teams that I form, contributing ideas and proposing solutions, I adapt easily to new work environments, I am constantly learning with the experience of the projects and also new technologies.

Experience

Software Engineer, Smith Chile, Santiago

December 2021 - Present

Developer on the SAP Commerce Cloud platform, using the Angular framework with typescript, and Spring with java. In extraordinary cases I have been made to work with applications based on ReactJS, and you adjust some pages with WordPress

SAP ABAP Developer, IBM Chile, Santiago

March 2019 - November 2021

SAP Developer as ABAP Developer, in which I was working on the ECC and S/4HANA versions, looking at migration and support projects, looking mainly at the MM/SD modules, I also saw some FIORI applications and adjustment of CDS views

Education

Ingeniería Ejecución en Software, Universidad Técnica Federico Santa María, Santiago

March 2019 - March 2022

Técnico universitario en Informática, Universidad Técnica Federico Santa María, Santiago

March 2016 - June 2019

Certifications

SAP Certified Development Professional - SAP Commerce Cloud 1905 Developer January 2022

SAP Certified Development Associate - ABAP with SAP NetWeaver 7.50 October 2021